Putri Balkis Mohamad Nor No. 12, Jalan Chepor Indah 35 Taman Chepor Indah 31200 Chemor Perak

General Manager Human Resources & Administration Majuperak Holdings Berhad Aras 1, Bazar Ipoh Jalan Sultan Nazrin Shah 31350 Ipoh Perak

20th August 2021

Dear Madam.

APPLYING FOR SPECIAL OFFICER TO GROUP CHIEF EXECUTIVE OFFICER POSITION

With reference to the above said matter, I would like to apply for the position of Special Officer to Group Chief Executive Officer in your esteemed company.

I am highly passionate, energetic, flexible, along with a positive attitude, and the ability to adapt quickly to new environment allows me to fit in the corporate field. 9 years' experience with third sector had built up my character to find solution and be responsive in any circumstances, also a self-directed, team player and goal-oriented doer.

I manage to learn and improve my organizational and management skills throughout the years, from brainstorming, paperwork writing and budgeting, managing volunteers, and strategic partners engagement. I am looking forward to transfer my skills and knowledge to the corporate business industry. I believe that I could leave a positive contribution to your team.

I would appreciate the opportunity to be interviewed by your respective company.

Thank You.

Best regard

(PUTRI BALKIS MOHAMAD NOR)

017-2849226



OBJECTIVE

Program Executive with over 9 years' experience in NGO looking to transfer my skills to the corporate business industry. My proven organizational and management skills make me an ideal fit for the Special Officer to Group CEO's position.

QUALIFICATION

2009-2012

Bachelor in Social Sciences with Honours (International Relations) Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia

WORK EXPERIENCE

Job Title : Program Officer

Organization : Malaysian youth Council

Duration : 2016 - present

Job Scope :

Design and organize youth related programs locally and internationally; volunteer, leadership, TVET, entrepreneurship. Strategic partners engagement.

Job Title : International Officer
Organization : Malaysian youth Council

Duration : 2012 - 2015

Job Scope :

Draft proposal, communicate with prospect partners and sponsors, manage participants, dealing with travel agency and most important executing program on the date.

PUTRI BALKIS MOHAMAD NOR

017-2849226 putri.balkis79@gmail.com 7th September 1990 31st Years Old Ipoh, Perak

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Organization & Team Work
- Interpersonal
- Problem Solving

INVOLVEMENT

2012 : Coordinator, United Nations Youth Assembly Program, United States

2013 : Delegates, UNESCO Youth Forum, France

2014 : Treasurer, Malaysian Humanitarian

Movemement (NGO)

2015 : Coordinator, Colors of ASEAN

2016 : Coordinator, Malaysia International

Youth Exchange

2017 : Coordinator, Malaysian Youth Volunteer

Community

2018 : Coordinator, General Election

Local Observer (PRU14)

2019 : Lay Kaunselor, KPWKM

2020 : Volunteer, Misi Relawan Covid-19

REFERENCES

Dr. Mohamed Maliki Mohamed Rapiee Director, International Youth Centre 019-384 1080 | iyckl.maliki@gmail.com

YB En Mohd Zaidi Aziz Secretary, Committee for ASEAN Youth Cooperation 019-448 6212 | mr_zaidiey@yahoo.com